Guide to the John Lowenthal Papers TAM.190
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Subject Files, 1942-2003
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 9, 1949; cuid8609 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 14, 1949; cuid8610 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 20, 1949; cuid8611 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 23, 1949; cuid8612 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 28, 1948; cuid8613 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jun 30, 1948; cuid8614 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Hiss Case: U.S.A. v. Alger Hiss, Stenographer's Minutes, Jul 6, 1949; cuid8615 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Hiss Case: Woodstock Typewriter, 1940s; cuid8616 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - The Hiss Case Revisited (JL): Handwritten Notes, undated; cuid8617 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - The Hiss Case Revisited (JL): Typescript, undated; cuid8618 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Introduction (Chapter 1), 1995; cuid8619 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Coram Nobis, 1987; cuid8620 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Drafts and Comments, 1987; cuid8621 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Notes, re:, 1982, 1992-1996; cuid8622 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Russia, 1998; cuid8623 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): The Typewriter, 1987; cuid8624 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Hiss Manuscript (JL): Whittaker Chambers' Homosexuality, undated; cuid8625 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Hiss, Tony: Re: Laughing Last, undated, 1976-1977; cuid8626 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Hiss, Tony: Writings, 1995-1996, 2001; cuid8627 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Hobson, Timothy, 1949-1950, 1968, 1977; cuid8628 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Hofstra University: International Conference on Harry S. Truman, Apr 14, 1983-Apr 16, 1983; cuid8629 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Horowitz, Sol, 1979-1980; cuid8630 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Howgate, James C.: HUAC Reports, Re:, Mar 1963; cuid8631 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hunt, Howard: Grand Jury Testimony, May 2, 1973; cuid8632 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Ilyashov, Anatoli Michael: Correspondence and Letter to the Editor, 1992-1994; cuid8633 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Intelligence and National Security: "Venona and Alger Hiss", 2000; cuid8634 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Kalugin, Oleg Danielovich: Clippings and Correspondence, 1992; cuid8635 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Kenan, George B., 1972, 1977, 1996-1999; cuid8636 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Kenshaw, Alex: The Guardian, 1992-1994; cuid8637 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Kinsley, Michael and Arthur Lubow: "Alger Hiss and the Smoking Gun Fallacy" (Washington Monthly), Oct 1975; cuid8638 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Kraft, Marion: Last Will and Testament, re:, 1982-1984; cuid8639 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Kraft, Marion: Motion Picture Editors, Local 771, 1978-1982; cuid8640 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Krieger, Sam: Chambers/Hiss, Re:, 1977-1982; cuid8641 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Krieger, Sam: Lawsuit Re: Perjury, 1978; cuid8642 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Lake, Anthony: CIA, 1977-1978; cuid8643 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lamphere, Robert J.: Book Excerpts and Notes, re:, 1983, 1986; cuid8644 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Leab, Daniel J.: "United We Eat: The Creation and Organization of the Unemployed Councils in 1930" (Labor History), Fall 1967; cuid8645 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Lee, Duncan, Eleanor and John: Correspondence and Letter to the Editor (New York Times), 1999; cuid8646 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Lee Pressman and David Witt, Typescript, 1998-1999; cuid8647 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Letters of Support: Re: Hiss, 1992-1993; cuid8648 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Letters to the Editor: Drafts, 1973; 1986; 1991-1993; cuid8649 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Letters to the Editor: Drafts, 1994; cuid8650 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Letters to the Editor: Drafts, 1995-2003; cuid8651 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Letters to the Editor: Published, 1992-2001; cuid8652 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Letters to the Editor: Re: Alger Hiss Obituaries, 1996; cuid8653 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Levin, David: Articles and Obituaries, 1976, 1979, 1993-1997; cuid8654 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Levin, David: Correspondence, 1993-1998; cuid8655 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Levine, Isaac Don, 1940-1999; cuid8656 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lockwood, Manice, III: Correspondence, undated, 1950-1953, 1969-1994; cuid8657 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Lowe, Richard H.: Correspondence, 1976, 1979; cuid8658 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Lowe, Richard H.: "Fallen Warrior of Reform: Jerome N. Frank as General Counsel for the Agricultural Adjustment Administration," Class Paper, undated; cuid8659 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Lowenthal, Anne: Correspondence, 1981, 2001; cuid8660 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Lowenthal, David: Correspondence, 1977-1980; cuid8661 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Lowenthal, Max, undated; cuid8662 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Lowenthal, Max: and Alger Hiss, 1995, 1998; cuid8663 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lowenthal, Max: Correspondence, 1940s; cuid8664 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Lowenthal, Max: Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) File, Jun 7, 1999; cuid8665 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 1, undated; cuid8666 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 6, undated; cuid8667 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 6 Bulky 576, undated; cuid8668 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 7, undated; cuid8669 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 8, undated; cuid8670 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File, Section 9, Part 1, undated; cuid8671 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Section 9, Part 2), undated; cuid8672 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Sections 9 and 10), undated; cuid8673 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Section 11), undated; cuid8674 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Section 12, Part 1), undated; cuid8675 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Section 12, Part 2), undated; cuid8676 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Lowenthal, Max: FOIA File (Sections 13 and 14), undated; cuid8677 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - MacArthur, John: Re: Harpers, 1992-1996, 2002-2003; cuid8678 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Marbury, William, 1976-1978, 1988; cuid8679 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Mark, Eduard: Reply from JL re: "Alger Hiss, The Perfect Victim", 2003; cuid8680 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Mark, Eduard: Reply from JL re: "Who Was Venona's 'Ales'? Cryptoanalysis and the Hiss Case", 2003; cuid8681 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Marshall Plan, 1997-1999; cuid8682 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Martino, Rose, 1966, 1969; cuid8683 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - McDowell, John: Correspondence, Jul 23, 1956; cuid8684 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Merillat, Herbert Christopher: Correspondence, 1995; cuid8685 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Miller, Larry: "Clarence Evan Pickett and the Alger Hiss Case," Typescript, undated; cuid8686 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Moor, Paul: Correspondence, 1992-1994; cuid8687 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Moore, William: Correspondence, 1988; cuid8688 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - The Movie, Typescript, Mar 1998; cuid8689 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Murphy, Robert C.: "The Hiss Case: Insights," Re:, undated, 1992-1993; cuid8690 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Murphy, Thomas F.: Correspondence, 1972, 1977-1978; cuid8691 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Murphy, Thomas: "Summation to the Jury: People of the United States v. Alger Hiss" (Plain Talk) Aug 1949, cuid8692 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Musmanno, Michael A.: That Chambers Book: With Comment on Communism, Alger Hiss and the State of Our Times, Pamphlet, undated; cuid8693 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Nation: Articles/Editorials, 1976, 1992, 1994; cuid8694 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Nation Institute: "Investigative Reporting after the Cold War," Conference, Moscow State University, Sep 4, 1992-Sep 7, 1992; cuid8695 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Nation Institute: Press Reactions to Nation Institute's Cold War Archive Hiss Project, Clippings, Oct 1992-Mar 1993; cuid8696 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - National Emergency Civil Liberties Committee: Correspondence, 1980, 1983; cuid8697 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - National Popular Government League: Report on the Illegal Practices of the U.S. Department of Justice, Pamphlet, May 1920; cuid8698 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - National Review: Re: Hiss, 1993; cuid8699 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Navasky, Victor: Correspondence, 1978-2001; cuid8700 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Navasky, Victor: Re: Communism, Hiss, 1978, 1996, 2000-2001; cuid8701 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Nedelkoff, Robert: Correspondence, undated, 1994; cuid8702 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Nelson, Lawrence J.: Correspondence, 1979; cuid8703 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - New Criterion: "Notes and Comments," re: Hiss, Dec 1992; cuid8704 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Newmyer, Jacqueline: "The Vindication of an Innocent Man", 1993; cuid8705 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Newshour with Jim Lehrer: Transcript re: Nixon Tapes, Jan 2, 1997; cuid8706 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Newsweek: Re: Hiss, 1992-1993; cuid8707 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Nezavisimaya Gazeta, 1992-1993; cuid8708 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Nixon, Richard: Re: Hiss, undated, 1992-1993; cuid8709 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Nixon, Richard: "The Hiss Case: A Lesson for the American People," Speech, Jan 26, 1950; cuid8710 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Nixon, Richard: Six Crises, Excerpts, 1962; cuid8711 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nixon's Manipulations in the Hiss-Chambers Case (JL): Typescript, undated; cuid8712 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Notes: Handwritten, re: Hiss Books, undated; cuid8713 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Oates, Titus: Handwritten Notes re:, undated, 2003; cuid8714 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Opinions-Editorials (JL), 1962, 1996, 2002; cuid8715 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Osann, H. E.: "The Alger Hiss Case," Correspondence and Typescript, 1964-1965; cuid8716 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Piel, Gerard: Clash of Civilizations, re:, 1999; cuid8717 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Pierce, Edward: Re: "Ales", undated, 1997-1998; cuid8718 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Pigman, Ward, 1948, 1977; cuid8719 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Political Cartoons: Dreyfus, Hiss, undated, 1950; cuid8720 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Political Cartoons: Permission to Reprint, 1970-2000; cuid8721 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Pollack, Louis: U.S.A. v. Carlos Ivan Llera Plaza, Wilfredo Acosta, Victor Rodriguez, 2002; cuid8722 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Popkin, Julie: Correspondence, 1992-1993; cuid8723 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Powers, Thomas, Re: Ales, undated; cuid8724 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Prelin, Igor, 1992; cuid8725 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Public Citizen Litigation Group: Re: Hiss, May 14, 1999; cuid8726 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Public Relations: Re: Hiss, undated, 1986, 1992-1993; cuid8727 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Publishers and Agents: Correspondence, 2001-2002; cuid8728 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Quinn, Hannah and James: Correspondence, 1995; cuid8729 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Rabinowitz, Victor: Correspondence, Nov 10, 1982; cuid8730 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Reuben, William A.: Correspondence, 1970-1989; cuid8731 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Reuben, William A.: Handwritten Notes, undated; cuid8732 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Introduction, undated; cuid8733 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 1, undated; cuid8734 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 2, undated; cuid8735 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 3, undated; cuid8736 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 4, undated; cuid8737 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 6, undated; cuid8738 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 8, undated; cuid8739 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 9, undated; cuid8740 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 10, undated; cuid8741 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 11, undated; cuid8742 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 12, undated; cuid8743 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 13, undated; cuid8744 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 14, undated; cuid8745 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 17, undated; cuid8746 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 18, undated; cuid8747 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 21, undated; cuid8748 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 22, undated; cuid8749 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 24, undated; cuid8750 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 25, undated; cuid8751 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 26, Dec 9, 1998; cuid8752 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 27, Nov 18, 1998; cuid8753 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 28, Apr 16, 1999; cuid8754 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 29, Aug 19, 1999; cuid8755 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 30, Nov 1, 2000; cuid8756 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 31, Nov 24, 1999; cuid8757 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 32, Apr 2, 2000; cuid8758 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 33, Oct 2000; cuid8759 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 34, undated; cuid8760 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reuben, William A.: Hiss/Chambers Typescript, Chapter 36, undated; cuid8761 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Reuben, William A.: Letters to the Editor, 1996, 1999; cuid8762 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Reuben, William A.: Nixon Typescript, Chapters 1-5, undated; cuid8763 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Reuben, William A.: Nixon Typescript, Chapters 6-8; 10-13, undated; cuid8764 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Reuben, William A.: Nixon Typescript, Chapters 14-17, undated; cuid8765 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Reuben, William A.: "Whittaker Chambers: An American Hero," Typescript, undated; cuid8766 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Riptide Communications: Correspondence, 1992; cuid8767 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Risen, James: Correspondence, 1993, 2003; cuid8768 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Roberts, R. M.: Correspondence, 1993; cuid8769 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Roddick, Ellen: Correspondence, Nov 1997; cuid8770 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Rodell, Fred: "Was Alger Hiss Framed?" (The Progressive), Apr 1952; cuid8771 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Rogers, Bill: Correspondence, 1983-1984; cuid8772 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Romerstein, Herbert: The Venona Secrets, re:, 1992-2001; cuid8773 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Rosenberg Case, 1951, 1962, 1974-1993; cuid8774 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Rosenwald, Harold: Correspondence, 1972-1977; cuid8775 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Rosenwald, Harold: "In the Matter of Alger Hiss," (Harvard Law School Bulletin), Fall 1975; cuid8776 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Roulhac, George Norman: FBI File, undated; cuid8777 (Box 19, Folder 19a)
  - Russian Archives: Conference and Trip, 1991-1992, 1998; cuid8778 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Russian Archives: Re: Hiss, 1992-1993; cuid8779 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Russian General Says Hiss Was No Spy (JL): Notes and Typescript, 1992; cuid8780 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Ryan, Clarke Sylvester, 1950, 1977; cuid8781 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Sachs, Nannette Pierson: Correspondence, Dec 23, 1996; cuid8782 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Salant, Stephen: Correspondence, 1976-2000; cuid8783 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Salant, Stephen: Writings re: Hiss, undated, 1974; cuid8784 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Sanders, Bernard: Correspondence, re: Hiss, Aug 31, 1992; cuid8785 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Sandilands, Roger J.: Re: Lauchlin Currie, 1999-2000; cuid8786 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Sayre, Nora, undated, 1998; cuid8787 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Scales, Junius: Handwritten Notes, re:, 1977; cuid8788 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Schmidt, Maria: Article Re: Hiss, 1993; cuid8789 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Schweizer, Werner: "Noel Field: The Fictitious Spy," Typescript, 1996; cuid8790 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Shapiro, Meyer: Re: Hiss, 1948-1949, 1967, 1977-1987; cuid8791 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Shattuck, John H.F.: Letter to the Editor, re: Hiss, Mar 19, 1976; cuid8792 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Shaw, Elizabeth: Re: Vincent Shaw, 1986-1987; cuid8793 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Sheehy, Margaret: "Joyous and Sorrowful," Typescript, 1984; cuid8794 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Shelley, Alexandra: Article Re: Hiss (East Hampton Star), 1993; cuid8795 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Silvermaster, Nathan Gregory: Handwritten Notes, re:, 2000; cuid8796 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Simes, Dmitri, 1993-1994, 1998; cuid8797 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Simon Meyer and Son, Inc.: Insurance Policy, 1980; cuid8798 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Smith, John Chabot: Correspondence, 1976; cuid8799 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Smith, John Chabot: Debate with Allen Weinstein, Opening Statement, Apr 3, 1976; cuid8800 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Soviet Historiography on the Hiss Case (JL): Typescript, 1994; cuid8801 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Speaker Program, 2000-2003; cuid8802 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Spectator: Correspondence re: Hiss Article, 1996-2000; cuid8803 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Stephens, Robert A. v. William F. Yeomens, undated; cuid8804 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Stevens, Alexander (aka Jay Peters/Alexander Goldberger): Correspondence, May 9, 1949; cuid8805 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Stevenson, Matthew: Correspondence, 1992-1993; cuid8806 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Stevenson, Matthew: "Dealing in Russia" (The American Scholar), 1993; cuid8807 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Stevenson, Matthew: "Letter from Serbia" (The American Scholar), 1992; cuid8808 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Stoessel, Frederic: Correspondence, Jul 1975; cuid8809 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Stoskopf, Alan: "The Cold War at Home: The Remarkable Case of Alger Hiss," School Paper, 1983; cuid8810 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Stripling, Robert: Pumpkin Film, 1977, 1980; cuid8811 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Summers, Anthony: Correspondence, 1998-2000; cuid8812 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Tanenhaus, Sam, 1992-1993, 1997, 1999; cuid8813 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Telephone Tapping, Aug 24, 1949; cuid8814 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Toledano, Ralph de: FBI Reports, 1949; cuid8815 (Box 20, Folder 2a)
  - Travel: Trip to Soviet Union, 1992; cuid8816 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Bibliographic Notes, undated; cuid8817 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Borovik, Artiom, 1992-1993; cuid8818 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Clippings, 1981; cuid8819 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Clippings, Negatives and Positives, 1940-1959; cuid8820 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: British Universities Film and Video Council, 2000-2003; cuid8821 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Chambers, Esther, 1977, 1986; cuid8822 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Cooke, Alistair, 1979-1980; cuid8823 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Correspondence, re:, 1977-1979; cuid8824 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Correspondence, re:, 1980-1981; cuid8825 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Day, James, Nov 1, 1977; cuid8826 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: de Antonio, Emile, 1976-1979; cuid8827 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Direct Cinema, 1992-1999; cuid8828 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Directors Note and Film Transcript, 2003; cuid8829 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Endnotes and Film Notes, undated; cuid8830 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Fariello, Griffin, 1996-2001; cuid8831 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Feinstein, Gussie, 1978-1980; cuid8832 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Frank, Victor Reno, 1977, 1979; cuid8833 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Funding/Grants, 1977; cuid8834 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Handwritten Notes, re:, 1970s; cuid8835 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Handwritten Notes, re:, 2002; cuid8836 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Herbert, F. Edward, 1976-1981; cuid8837 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: HUAC, 1976; cuid8838 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Inquiries, 1994-2000; cuid8839 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Ladd, Helen, 1977, 1979; cuid8840 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Lamb, Edward, 1976, 1979; cuid8841 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Levin, Alvin, 1979; cuid8842 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Lindau, Alfred M., 1977; cuid8843 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Media Study, Buffalo, 1981-1982; cuid8844 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Mischel, Larry, 1977, 1979; cuid8845 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Murtaugh, Edward S., 1977, 1979; cuid8846 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Newsreels, undated, 1976-1977, 1983; cuid8847 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Nixon, Richard, 1976-1977; cuid8848 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Outtakes, 1970-1999; cuid8849 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Photographs, Search for, 1994; cuid8850 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Promotions/Publicity/Distribution, International, 1980-1994; cuid8851 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Promotions/Publicity, National, undated, 1979-1982; cuid8852 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Releases, 1977-1979; cuid8853 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Schmitt, Joseph, 1977; cuid8854 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Script Additions, 2002; cuid8855 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Script Annotations, 1979; cuid8856 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Script Changes, 1983; cuid8857 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Shapero, Harold, 1977, 1984; cuid8858 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Shaw, Vincent, 1978; cuid8859 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Silk, Lawrence, 1977; cuid8860 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Smith, John Chabot, undated, 1976; cuid8861 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Sound/Tape Reports, 1976-1977; cuid8862 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Spencer, Thomas G., 1949, 1977; cuid8863 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Strauss, Robert S., Aug 1992; cuid8864 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Stock Footage, undated, 1970s; cuid8865 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Stripling, Robert, 1977, 1980; cuid8866 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Sullivan, William, 1975, 1977; cuid8867 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Taylor, Duncan Norton, undated, 1977; cuid8868 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Timeline, undated; cuid8869 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Transcript, 1979; cuid8870 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Typescript, p. 1-100, 1979; cuid8871 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Typescript, p. 101-214, 1979; cuid8872 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Tytell Typewriter, 1976-1977; cuid8873 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: University of California, Berkeley, Pacific Film Archive, undated; cuid8874 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: von Werner, Robert, 1977; cuid8875 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Trials of Alger Hiss: Witt, Nathan, 1976-1977, 1982; cuid8876 (Box 22, Folder 4)